A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, Audiovisual Materials, RG 7 FA1801
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Photographs, 1890-2019; 5; 5.08 Cubic Feet 12 containers
  - People, 1890-2019; 4; 3.18 Cubic Feet 7 containers
    - Staff, 1982-2019; 5
      - Lawrence, Belinda Turner, 1997-2012 (Box 1, Folder 36)
        Color and b/w portraits of Belinda Lawrence, VP & Chief Administrative Officer, 1997 -- (4 items). Also, photos of Belinda with Rolfe Neill and Penny McPhee, and with Alvah Chapman and Creed Black.
      - Lee-Sin, Donovan, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 37)
        Knight File Number - 2835
        Color portrait of Donovan Lee-Sin, Program Assistant, 2001-2005 (1 copy).
      - Lewis, Janice Howard, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 38)
        Knight File Number - 2836
        B/w portrait of Janice Lewis, Journalism Program Assistant, 1991 - 2003 (1 copy and 1 neg).
      - Loflin, Katherine Torres, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 39)
        Knight File Number - 2837
        Color portrait of Katherine Loflin, Content Program Officer, 2001- 2007 (3 copies).
      - Maidenberg, Michael, 2004 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        Knight File Number - 2794
        Small, passport-type photos (B&W) of Mike Maidenberg; two pictures of Maidenberg speaking at Columbia University (b&w); color negatives of Maidenberg, while KF trustee and a series of color portraits (thumbnails and cd) taken in 2004 upon his promotion to vice president of Programs.
      - Maidenberg, Michael, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Maldonado, Patricia, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        Knight File Number - 2838
        Color portrait of Patricia Maldonado, Communications Manager, 2002 - 2004 (4 copies).
      - Martinez, Jorge (George), 1996-2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        Knight File Number - 2839
        Color portraits of George Martinez, Director of IT, 1996 -- (4 copies and 1 neg).
      - Martinez, Juan, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        Knight File Number - 2840
        Color portrait of Juan Martinez, VP of Accounting & Treasurer (formerly controller), 2002 -- (4 copies).
      - McPhee, Penelope, 1995-2004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        Knight File Number - 2841
        Color and b/w portraits of Penny McPhee, VP and Chief Program Officer, 1990 - 2004 (12 items). Includes cd of 2004 portrait.
      - McPhee, Penelope, 2004 February 6 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - McPhee, Penelope Tribute, 2004 March 26 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        Knight File Number - 4556
        Program and cd program honoring Penny McPhee. 4 cds.
      - McPhee, Penelope Tribute (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Meyer, Lawrence (Bud), 1995-2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        Knight File Number - 2842
        Color and b/w portraits of Larry Meyer, VP of Communications, 1995 -- (11 items & 2 negs).
      - Mojica, Virginia, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        Knight File Number - 2843
        Color portrait of Virginia Mojica, Investment Assistant, 2002-2006 -- (4 copies).
      - Neal, Vivian Celeste, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        Knight File Number - 2844
        Color portrait of Vivian Celeste Neal, Community Liaison Program Officer, 2002 -- (4 copies).
      - Neuhart, Phyllis, 1997-2004 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        Knight File Number - 2845
        Color portrait of Phyllis Neuhart, executive secretary to President, 1990 - 2004 (neg only). Also includes two photos of her farewell party (one with Creed Black).
      - Newton, Eric, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        Knight File Number - 2846
        Color portrait of Eric Newton, Director of Journalism Initiatives, 2001 -- (3 copies) and 1 photo from his tenure with the Newseum. Also includes 18 color photos of Eric "action" photos: in meetings, and speaking to a group.
      - Nieto-Winzey, Tanya, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        Knight File Number - 2847
        Color portrait of Tanya Nieto-Winzey, Journalism Program Assistant, 2002 - 2004.
      - Noble, Lynne, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        Knight File Number - 2848
        Color portrait of Lynne Noble, Administration Assistant, 1996 -- 2007 (neg only).
      - Pashenko, Asya, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        Knight File Number - 2849
        Color portrait of Asya Pashenko, Controller, 2000 - 2004 (4 copies).
      - Patterson, Susan, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        Knight File Number - 2850
        Color portrait of Susan Patterson, Community Liaison Program Officer, 2001 -- (3 copies)
      - Perry, Maurice, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        Knight File Number - 2851
        Color portrait of Maurice Perry, Director of Investment, 2001 -- 2006 (4 copies and 1 neg).
      - Perry-Smith, Susan, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        Knight File Number - 2852
        Color portrait of Susan Perry-Smith, Communications assistant, 2002 - 2005 (3 copies).
      - Popham, Erik, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 18)
        Knight File Number - 2853
        Color portrait of Eric Popham, Investment Officer, 2002 - 2006 (4 copies).
      - Prude (Harvey), Suzette, 1998-c.2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
        Knight File Number - 2854
        Color and b/w portraits of Suzette Prude, Community Liaison Program Officer, 1998 - 2005 (3 copies and negs). Note: Suzette's last name changed to Harvey in 2005
      - Rettig, Heidi, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        Knight File Number - 2855
        Color portrait of Heidi Rettig, Content Program Officer, 2001-2003 (2 copies).
      - Rostant, Ava Christian Guzman, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        Knight File Number - 2856
        Color portrait of Ava Christian Guzman Rostant, Executive Secretary, Investment Department, 2000-2007 (2 copies).
      - Sawyer, Reba, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        Knight File Number - 2857
        Color portrait of Reba Sawyer, receptionist, 1997 -- (negative only).
      - Sellers, Angelique, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        Knight File Number - 2858
        Color portrait of Angelique Sellers, Investment Assistant, 2001-2006 (2 copies).
      - Sklaroff, Lizabeth, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
        Knight File Number - 2859
        Color snapshots of Lizabeth Sklaroff, Content Program Officer, 1998-2005 (3 items).
      - Smith, Rhemila, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 25)
        Knight File Number - 2860
        Color portrait of Rhemila Smith, Archive, Record & Library Assistant, 2003-2004 (2 copies).
      - Spaniolo, James, 1990-1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
        Knight File Number - 939
        Portraits (for annual reports) and negatives of James Spaniolo, Vice-President and Secretary of KF, 1990s. Black & white and color.
      - Stewart, David, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        Knight File Number - 941
        Photographs of David Stewart, accounting manager, 1993. Black & white.
      - Talen, Polly M., 2002 (Box 2, Folder 28)
        Knight File Number - 2861
        Color portrait of Polly M. Talen, Community Liaison Program Officer, 2002 -- (3 copies).
      - Tarr, Julie, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 29)
        Knight File Number - 2862
        Color portrait of Julie Tarr, Community Liaison Program Officer, 2001 -- (1 copy).
      - Versaci, Lisa, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 30)
        Knight File Number - 2863
        Color portrait of Lisa Versaci, Director of National Venture Fund, 2002-2005 (3 copies).
      - White, Ellen, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        Knight File Number - 2864
        Color portrait of Ellen White, Journalism Program Assistant, 2002-2003 (2 copies).
      - Williams, John R. II, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 32)
        Knight File Number - 2865
        Color and b/w portraits of John Williams, Community Liaison Program Officer, 2001-2006(7 items).
    - Trustees, 1941-2008; 6
      - Alvarez, Cesar L., 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        Knight File Number - 2792
        Three black and white and one color portrait of KF trustee, Cesar Alvarez.
      - Austen, Gerald, 1993-2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        Knight File Number - 913
        Photographs of Dr. Gerald Austen, Knight Foundation Trustee, taken for 1993 annual report by Pelham Photographers. Also includes other undated photos, black & white and a collection of family photographs of Austen, his wife Patty, children and grandchildren, his mother, Bertl Arnstein, and colleagues at Harvard and Mass General Hospital.
      - Batten, James K., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        Knight File Number - 914
        Photographs of James K. (Jim) Batten, KF Trustee: one undated portrait, photos taken for 1993 annual report by Pelham Photographic Services. Black & white.
      - Briggs, Rob, 2003 March 12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        Knight File Number - 4552
        Color portraits of KF trustee, Rob Briggs. Also includes a cd with his photos and those of KF trustee Mariam Noland.
      - Briggs, Rob - Briggs and Noland, 2003 March 12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Chapman, Alvah, 1993-2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        Knight File Number - 918
        Photographs of Alvah Chapman, KF trustee: one undated photo (2 copies), one taken for 1993 annual report by Pelham Photographic Services, and one taken about 2000. Black & white and color.
      - Conway, Jill, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        Knight File Number - 919
        Photographs of Jill Conway, KF trustee, taken for 1993 annual report by Pelham Photographic Services. Black & white. Also includes several undated portraits, black and white and color.
      - Crane, Marjorie Knight, 1994-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
        Knight File Number - 920
        Photographs of Marjorie Knight Crane, KF trustee, taken for 1994 annual report by Pelham Photographic Services. Black & white. Also includes a later, undated, portrait, in black and white and color and a color photo c. 2000.
      - Gibson, Charles Colmery, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
        Knight File Number - 923
        Photograph of Charles Colmery (C.C.) Gibson, former president and trustee, taken for 1993 annual report by Pelham Photographic Services. Black & white.
      - Grogan, Paul S., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        Knight File Number - 2793
        Three black and white portraits of KF trustee, Paul Grogan.
      - Harris, Jay, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        Knight File Number - 926
        Photographs of Jay Harris, KF Trustee, for 1994 annual report by Pelham Photographic Services. Black & white.
      - Heffern, Gordon, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        Knight File Number - 927
        Photographs of Gordon Heffern, KF Trustee, for 1993 annual report by Pelham Photographic Services. Black & white. Plus an undated (later) portrait, black and white and color.
      - Hills, Lee, 1960-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
        Knight File Number - 929
        Photographs of Lee Hills, Trustee, Vice-Chairman and Chairman, 1960-1999. Photographs include portraits taken for annual reports and a photograph of Hills with President John F. Kennedy. Black & white and color. Negatives
      - Jinks, Larry, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        Knight File Number - 930
        Photographs of Larry Jinks, Trustee, for 1992 and 1993 annual report. Also informal photo at unidentified event with young children (1990s?). Black & white.
      - Johnson, Thomas, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        Knight File Number - 931
        Photographs of Thomas Johnson, Trustee, taken for 1993 annual report by Pelham Photographic Services. Black & white.
      - McDowell, C. Blake, 1941 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        Knight File Number - 2791
        C. Blake McDowell and Smith Davis at the Miami Herald.
      - Neill, Rolfe, 1995-2005 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        Knight File Number - 934
        Photographs of Rolfe Neill, Charlotte, NC advisor, and Trustee. Black & white and color; most undated. Also included is a series of digital photos (cd included) of Rolfe Neill posing at the momument to him at the Charlotte Observer (2005).
      - Neill, Rolfe - Sculpture, 2005 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Noland, Mariam C., 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        Knight File Number - 2795
        Black and white and color photos of KF trustee, Mariam C. Noland.
      - Olson, Beverly Knight, 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        Knight File Number - 935
        Photographs of Beverly Knight Olson, trustee, taken for 1993 annual report by Pelham Photographic Services. Black & white. Also includes other undated portraits, color.
      - Ong, John, 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
        Knight File Number - 936
        Photograph of John D. Ong, trustee, taken for the 1995 annual report. Black & white. Also included are two other portraits, one b/w and one color, approximately 2000.
      - Rogers, John W., Jr., 1999 December (Box 1, Folder 20)
        Knight File Number - 2796
        Color and black and white photograph of KF trustee, John Rogers.
      - Stanford, Henry King, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
        Knight File Number - 940
        Photographs of Henry King Stanford, trustee. Includes annual report portraits (1993) and candid shots at meetings. Black & white.
      - Toomey, Barbara Knight, 1986-1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
        Knight File Number - 942
        Photographs of Barbara Knight Toomey, trustee, ca. 1986-1993. Includes annual report portraits. Black & white.
    - Groups, 1970-2014; 7
      - Board of Trustees, 1986 June (Box 1, Folder 1)
        Knight File Number - 1390
        B/W group portrait of Board of Trustees (Alvah Chapman, Barbara Knight Toomey, Henry King Stanford, C.C. Gibson, Gordon Heffern, Lee Hills, and James Knight (includes color slide and negative).
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        Knight File Number - 945
        Undated group photographs of Knight Foundation staff members Shirley Follo and David Catrow and Shirley Follo and an unidentified woman (earlier than first photo). Black & white.
      - Board of Trustees: Meetings and Portraits, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        Knight File Number - 943
        Group photographs of the Board of Trustees for the 1990 annual report (taken at Board meetings). Included are Barbara Knight Toomey, Rolfe Neill, Gerald Austen, Jim Batten and Alvah Chapman. Black & white.
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        Knight File Number - 2404
        Group photographs (by program area and/or department) of Knight Foundation staff members for the 1990 annual report. Includes Creed Black, Phyllis Neuhart, Jenny Henke, Kay Simpson, Peggy Smith, Tim Crowe, Penny McPhee, Naida Gonzalez, Rick Love. Black & white.
      - Board of Trustees, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        Knight File Number - 947
        Group photograph of the Board of Trustees for the 1991 annual report. Includes Jill Conway, Tom Johnson, Creed Black, Gordon Heffern, Rolfe Neill, Beverly Knight Olson, Jim Batten, Alvah Chapman, Barbara Toomey, Henry King Stanford, C.C. Gibson, Gerald Austen, and Lee Hills. Black & white.
      - Knight Foundation Board of Trustees, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
        Knight File Number - 2521
        Four black and white portraits (12"x14") of members of the Board of Trustees taken for the 1991 Annual Report.
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        Knight File Number - 2405
        Group photographs (by program area and/or department) of Knight Foundation staff members for the 1991 annual report. Includes Creed Black, Phyllis Neuhart, Jenny Henke, Kay Simpson, Peggy Smith, Tim Crowe, Penny McPhee, Naida Gonzalez, Rick Love. Black & white.
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members and Family Day, 1991 October (Box 1, Folder 7)
        Knight File Number - 2467
        Informal photographs of Knight Foundation staff and family members taken at Family Day (on a fishing boat). Color
      - Knight Foundation Board of Trustees, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        Knight File Number - 2522
        Four black and white portraits (12"x14") of members of the Board of Trustees taken for the 1992 Annual Report.
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
        Knight File Number - 2403
        Group photographs (by program area and/or department) of Knight Foundation staff members for the 1992 annual report. Includes Creed Black, Phyllis Neuhart, Jenny Henke, Stacey Condit, Kay Simpson, Linda Raybin, David Singer, Peggy Smith, Tim Crowe, Shawn Tucker, Penny McPhee, Hildee Wilson, Naida Gonzalez, Rick Love, Rita Meghoo, Jim Spaniolo. Black & white.
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members Family Fun Day, 1992 October (Box 1, Folder 9)
        Knight File Number - 2472
        Informal photographs of Knight Foundation staff and family members taken at Family Day (on a boat). Color
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        Knight File Number - 948
        Group photographs (by program area and/or department) of Knight Foundation staff members for the 1993 annual report. Includes Creed Black, Phyllis Neuhart, Jenny Henke, Stacey Condit, Kay Simpson, Linda Raybin, David Stewart, Peggy Smith, Tim Crowe, Shawn Tucker, Penny McPhee, Hildee Wilson, Naida Gonzalez, Rick Love. Black & white.
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        Knight File Number - 949
        Group photographs (by program area and/or department) of Knight Foundation staff members for the 1994 annual report. Includes Janice Howard, Del Brinkman, Rita Meghoo, Jim Spaniolo, Sherri Beuchert, Keith Landon, Maurice Perry, Creed Black, Phyllis Neuhart, Jenny Henke, Stacey Condit, Kay Simpson, Linda Raybin, David Stewart, Peggy Smith, Tim Crowe, Shawn Tucker, Penny McPhee, Hildee Wilson, Naida Gonzalez, Rick Love. Black & white.
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
        Knight File Number - 950
        Group photographs (by program area and/or department) of Knight Foundation staff members for the 1995 annual report. Includes Alfredo Cruz, Robert Kevers, Janice Howard, Del Brinkman, Keith Landon, Maurice Perry, Creed Black, Phyllis Neuhart, Bud Meyer, Kay Simpson, Linda Raybin, Peter Sahwell, Peggy Smith, Tim Crowe, Shawn Tucker, Penny McPhee, Hildee Wilson, Naida Gonzalez, Rick Love, James Spaniolo, Stacey Condit-Campbell, Rita Meghoo, Sherri Beuchert. Black & white.
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        Knight File Number - 2468
        Informal photographs of Knight Foundation staff and family members taken at: Baby Shower for Keith Landon Shawn Tucker with Son Halloween Rick Love Hildee Wilson and Keith Landon with children Color
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        Knight File Number - 3853
        Group photographs (by program area and/or department) of Knight Foundation staff members for the 1996 annual report. Includes Alfredo Cruz, Robert Kevers, Janice Howard, Del Brinkman, Maurice Perry, Creed Black, Phyllis Neuhart, Kay Simpson, Linda Raybin, Peter Sahwell, Peggy Smith, Marion Jones, Lynne Noble, Tim Crowe, Shawn Tucker, Penny McPhee, Hildee Wilson, George Martinez, Naida Gonzalez, Rick Love, Julia Van, J. Bryan McCullar, Rita Meghoo, Larry Meyer. and Judy Bernstein. Black & white.
      - Knight Foundation Reception at Davidson College, 1997 November (Box 1, Folder 15)
        Knight File Number - 2797
        B/W group portrait of Penny McPhee, Rolfe Neill, Tom Wicker, Rick Love and Marjorie Knight Crane.
      - Knight Foundation Journalism Advisory Committee, 2003 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        Knight File Number - 4555
        Color portraits of of individual members and a group shot. Includes cd. Members are: Sandra Mims Rowe, Merrill Brown, Barbara Cochran, John Dotson, Rich Oppel, Geneva Overholser, Jim Spaniolo and James Risser.
      - Knight Foundation Journalism Advisory Committee - JAC Portraits, 2003 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Albert Ibarguen and Gerald Austen - Thumbnail Prints, 2006 March 12 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        Knight File Number - 5874
        Series of color pictures of Alberto Ibarguen and Gerald Austen taken for the 2005 annual report. Photos were taken in KF office in Miami and some feature the portrait of the Knight brothers. A few include trustee Mariam Noland. Disc and contact sheets.
      - Albert Ibarguen and Gerald Austen, 2006 March (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Knight Foundation Trustees and Staff - Thumbnail Prints, 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        Knight File Number - 4554
        Color portraits of trustees and staff. Also included are a small number of photographs of Dr. Austen, and photos of Mike Maidenberg and Reba Sawyer retirement parties.
      - Knight Foundation Staff with Trustees, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Knight Foundation Trustees, 2007 March (Box 1, Folder 19)
        Knight File Number - 4553
        Color portraits of some of the trustees and some informal pictures of trustees, spouses and staff. Includes 2 cds.
      - Knight Foundation Trustees, David Gergen by Mark Wilson, 2007 March (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Knight Foundation Trustees by Mark Wilson (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Knight Foundation Communications/Journalism Team, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 20)
        Knight File Number - 5633
        Photo of a group of KF staffers, including Jose Zamora, Marc Fest, Stuart Kennedy, and Gary Kebbel.
      - Knight Foundation Communications Department, 2014 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 21)
        Knight File Number - 5304
        Restricted - Open 2025
        Three color prints of Communications Department posing in the KF boardroom. From left, Chris Vastine, Michael Bolden, Anushka Alikhan, Elizabeth Miller, Mariska Lynch, Eric Shoenborn, Andrew Sherry, and Robertson Adams.
      - John S. Knight and Lee Hills, c. 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        Knight File Number - 4968
        John S. Knight and Lee Hills on the occasion of Knight being awarded an honorary doctorate. Photo is inscribed, "Let's always be a couple of winners. Best, Jack". B/W print, 8" x 11", mounted in foam core matting.
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members, 2000 December 15 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        Knight File Number - 2475
        Photograph album contains invitations, menu, favors, photos and decorations for Knight Foundation's annual holiday party. Color
      - Knight Foundation Staff Members - Winterfest Boat Parade, 2001 December 15 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        Knight File Number - 2476
        Photograph album contains invitations, photos and artwork for Knight Foundation's annual holiday party. This year it was held in conjunction with the Winterfest Boat Parade. Color
      - Knight Foundation Staff with Yale University Visitors, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
        Knight File Number - 2283
        (left to right, back row) Creed Black, Jim Spaniolo, Carroll Stevens (Yale), Del Brinkman. (left to right, front) Lee Hills and the Yale Law School Dean (name unknown). Color
  - Programs, 1982-2006; 5; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - Arts and Culture, 1994-1995; 1
      - Arts & Culture Program in Annual Report, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        Knight File Number - 872
        Photographs taken of the Arts & Culture Program for the Annual Report, 1994. Includes a photo of Josi Callan of the San Jose Museum of Art (by Anne Knudsen), and Michael Tilson Thomas of the New World Symphony (by Clive Barda). Black & white.
      - Arts & Culture Program, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        Knight File Number - 873
        Photographs taken, but not used, of the Arts & Culture Program for the Annual Report, 1994. Black & white.
      - Arts & Culture: New World Symphony, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        Knight File Number - 881
        Photograph of Michael Tilson Thomas and the New World Symphony taken for the cover of the 1994 Annual Report. Photo by Bob Gelberg. Black & white.
      - Arts & Culture Program, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        Knight File Number - 883
        Photographs taken of the Arts & Culture program in 1995, but not used in any publication. Includes photos of Penelope McPhee and Creed Black. Black & white.
    - Community Initiatives, 1993-1994; 2
      - Community Initiatives: Habitat for Humanity, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)